C

pooja7492@gmail.com



Behance.net/poojajhunjhu



Jersey City



I am a UI designer with a background in pastry art, human development, fashion, and interior design. I was born & raised in India and I have always been passionate about design and creativity. I am experienced in communicating with customers and dedicated to understanding what clients want and need. I empathize with clients and take pride in my organizational skills and attention to detail. I aim to create beautiful and user intuitive designs.

EXPERIENCE

POOJA

UI DESIGNER

JHUNJHUNWALA

Plated Pixie dust-Recipe Developer & Blogger

2019 to now / Website: www.platedpixiedust.com/ Platforms: @platedpixiedust

- Develop recipes for my blog and designed my website using Squarespace.
- Write and create my content, including editing pictures and videos for each recipe
- Share my product on social media platforms such a Instagram, Youtube, Pinterest and TikTok.
- Analyze data pertaining to my posts to create content based on engagement, post timing, etc.
- Partner with brands to create and share content.

Cake by Pooja- Founder and Head Baker

2016 to 2019/ Kolkata, India

- Started my home bakery in Kolkata after finishing my Pastry and Cake decorating Diplomas. Grew the business by hiring 2 interns.
- Designed and baked cakes and pastries as per clients requests, making their visions come true.
- Exhibited time management and client handling skills, managing deadlines, communicating, and accepting orders to be sent out on time.
- Created the social media content and creatives on platforms like Canva & Wix.

Onset Retail store-Intern and Event Managing

November 2011- April 2012/ Kolkata, India

- Interned in a home decor and tactile store and increased overall sales.
- Planned and managed two large scale events for the store-Andalusia- a Spanish themed festival and a book your portrait shoot

AWARDS

- 2nd place in the US Junior Pastry Competition 2016- 1st Indian to place
- Top toque in both Pastry arts and Cake decorating Diploma
- Valedictorian in my Bachelors of Science program

SKILLS & TOOLS

Sketch Invision Balsamia Flinto Keynote iMovie **User Flows** Competitor Analysis Wire framing Prototyping **Usability Testing** Style Guides & Color schemes Iconography Typography Branding Responsive Design`

EDUCATION

CareerFoundry 2020 - 2021

UI Design Program Specialization: Front end Development.

Institute of Culinary Education,NYC 2015-2016

Pastry & Baking Diploma Cake Decoration Diploma

JD Birla Institute, Kolkata 2012-2015

Bsc in Home Science

LANGUAGE

English, Hindi, Bengali